{
    "id": "dffc529a54244cdb81711365feb717ac",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She went to the market and bought some eggs. Here went is a ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "adverb",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I want to go now. Here now is a/an ..............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "adjective",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What are you doing there? Here there is a/an ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a mouse underneath the piano. Underneath is a/an ........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "conjunction",
                "preposition",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Masons build houses. Masons is a/an .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "adverb",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "John is my best friend. Here John is a/an ........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Proper noun",
                "Collective noun",
                "Common noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She looked up but didn’t see anything.  Here up is a/an ............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "adverb",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My family live in different parts of India.  Here family is a/an ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "abstract noun",
                "collective noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "That was a difficult question. Here difficult is a/an ...........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She was very impressed with her results. Here very is a/an ...............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Although she is poor, she is happy. Although is a/an ............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "conjunction",
                "preposition",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Have we bought enough chairs? Enough is a/an ..............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adverb",
                "adjective",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The policeman didn’t run fast enough to catch the thief.  Here fast is a/an .........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}